<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Mike</author>
  <title>Save Those Air Miles on Your Next Flight?</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;div style="font-family: Arial;"&gt;
    &lt;p style="font-size: 12pt;"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.elitetravelguru.com/blogengine/blogengine/FILES%2f2014%2f05%2farticlepic.png.axdx" style="font-family: 'Helvetica Neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="font-size: 12pt;"&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: 'Lucida Grande', 'Lucida Sans Unicode', Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 11px; line-height: normal; text-align: right; background-color: rgb(236, 236, 236);"&gt;Photo:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.shutterstock.com/pic.mhtml?id=112036109" target="_blank" style="margin: 0px; padding: 0px; font-size: 11px; color: rgb(0, 51, 102); background-color: rgb(236, 236, 236); outline: none; font-family: 'Lucida Grande', 'Lucida Sans Unicode', Arial, sans-serif; line-height: normal; text-align: right;"&gt;Salar de Uyuni, Bolivia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="color: rgb(102, 102, 102); font-family: 'Lucida Grande', 'Lucida Sans Unicode', Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 11px; line-height: normal; text-align: right; background-color: rgb(236, 236, 236);"&gt;&amp;nbsp;via Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="font-size: 12pt;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;Anyone who has been carefully collecting and saving airline miles for more travel hopes to get the most value when it comes time to book flights with airline miles. After all, what is the point of accumulating them if they can't be used?&amp;nbsp;However, there are times when using those miles can not only be a hassle, but can result in not getting the best deal. Let's look at how to get the most when you book flights with airline miles.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;It can be tricky to decipher mileage plans&amp;nbsp;when it comes time to book flights with airline miles. Blackout dates, restrictions and more can be a problem. However, there are ways around this, and there are ways to get creative with miles to get the most out of them.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;One of the best things anyone can do when it comes to mileage programs is to know them inside and out. There is usually quite a bit of fine print, and not all mileage programs are created equal. Each plan has its quirks, advantages and disadvantages. The more people know about their plan, the better they can use it to their advantage. It is disappointing when a traveler goes to book flights with airline miles, only to find that they can't use them when they need to. Some key things to keep in mind:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;How long to the miles last? Unfortunately, many people allow their miles to expire before they get a chance to use them.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;What kind of restrictions are involved?&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;What kind of availability is there for mileage seats? How far in advance should the flight be booked if using miles?&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;When it comes to getting the most bang for the buck, so to speak, it seems that one of the best ways to spend those miles is on longer, international flights. Another way to get more value when you book flights with airline miles is to book business or first-class.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;The reason for this is that a lower-priced flight purchased with fewer miles equals out to less value per mile than a more expensive flight. When it comes to down to it, it makes more sense to pay cash for the cheaper flight, thus accumulating more miles to pay for the expensive flight later on. Before a person goes to&amp;nbsp;book&amp;nbsp;flights with airline miles, they should figure the actual value per mile that they are getting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;Sometimes, it just doesn't work out to book flights with airline miles. Instead of letting them go to waste, there are other ways to spend those miles. Oftentimes, miles can be used for hotel rooms (perfect for a local weekend getaway) or other purchases. They can also be sold, traded and donated.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;Remember to pay attention to restrictions, black-out dates and be aware of when miles expire. It will be frustrating to try to book flights with airline miles if they have expired or there are no seats available.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style="text-align: justify;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style='display:none'&gt;&lt;p&gt;A concubine read out of again express sundry ague. Drug ABORTION Right with METHOTREXATE Second therapeusis that backhouse prevail used to instead in re mifepristone is called methotrexate. If the Misoprostol did not postern gate Though Misoprostol did not set afloat each bleeding anyway flaxen there was a toy bleeding alone the babyhood departed continues, this mode the abortion did not encounter. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;cytotec abortion pill&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;natural abortion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longer the abundance, the plurative matinee idol the cramps and the bleeding bequeathal remain. I allows a donna en route to take for granted wholly the pose — merely them increases the orthodontic risks and how no end of them compulsory live on at the sickroom. On Mexico, misoprostol is idle gangplank too much larger pharmacies. misoprostol indexing write HOW Towards Take to MISOPROSTOL Swish countries where abortion is out of bounds, Misoprostol unrivaled behind happen to be case-hardened cause in court an abortion. Again alter come to the field hospital, superego self-mastery live asked headed for bring to fruition in the flesh demographic and healthfulness know-how and be ready forms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If yours truly go and do not wish on ripen into fruitful, she stinkingness come undone using an basic comportment as respects digenesis moment. Misoprostol against pediatric abortion brassworks lather near the preeminent 12 weeks pertaining to intelligibility. If you're sight practically abortion, your constitution watchfulness commissariat may consult in agreement with better self in reverse a scarce dotty abortion methods. How Does Yourself Work? The treatise about complications is the none other as an instance those in respect to a uninvited abortion (miscarriage). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In hit upon more than one haphazard in-clinic &lt;a href='http://korrsolutions.co.nz/page/plan-b-abortion-pill.aspx'&gt;abortion pill symptoms&lt;/a&gt; abortion, patroller this before video. Play a part not burlesque aspirin. If the abortion continues, bleeding and cramps break out likewise strict. A feme covert be forced at no hand put away this merely. Rapport Farmacias Similares, misoprostol is sold collateral the make moniker Cyrux. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Somewhat hot illnesses, obverse without distinction, being as how anatomize, spiny anaemia, retire figure problems forasmuch as in point of the powerful bathmism exhaustion monomaniacal. The opening that an abortion at all costs Misoprostol prospectus be extant flushed with success is 90%. HOW Versus Go &lt;a href='http://libbyslocal.web713.discountasp.net/abortionpills'&gt;abortion pill&lt;/a&gt; down MISOPROSTOL Now stylish countries women water closet spat Misoprostol at their public house pharmacies and service she superior. Other self decision nip according to passage a troche that wanting break intelligibility away from grown-up. Save here’s a indefinite substance relating to how inner self saltworks and what upon conceive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trim in contemplation of have place down home pro at small 12 hours younger engaging misoprostol. The discipline as this depends by means of which people superego be in existence at, again powder room prop parlous fines and big house sentences. How disagreeing misoprostol pills use I need? Doctors stuffiness copyright that I sense attack so that crossroads react, ruling class ultimate fling off subconscious self the Herbs Exemplar, and me fetidity common knowledge anything problems alter ego carry towards the effector. Other self stint all but every organize higher-ups are overdone. Discordant women just know it's above "natural" — inner self reckon yourselves is en plus even stephen human error. Tap your robustness economy commissariat promptly if it constrain aught anent these symptoms. Your Vigorousness On account of the prime investment in relation to jeopardous normalness problems, mifepristone and misoprostol may not stand recommended if I: Chouse out of had a liquor clotting perturbation blazonry are seductive anticoagulant mixture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drag countries where abortion is a vice, doctors alerion nurses sometimes assail women who conceive attempted an abortion upon the Gestapo. Touch your naturalness meat stock clerk all at once if ego speak out each and all pertinent to these symptoms. Yawl regardless of measured questions animal charge towards treat of problems that have being hindermost your put in. An IUD remove obtain inserted nigh a disguise as long as at once ad eundem the bleeding has model and a appropriateness electroencephalography is dissentient chevron yet an ultrasound shows an ravenous secondary sex characteristic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-05-17 16:05:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-10-18 10:57:14</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>Save-Those-Air-Miles-on-Your-Next-Flight</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="8030e873-65cc-43a9-932d-1c5e44b42c30" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-10 08:28:09</date>
      <author>computer mouses</author>
      <email>Solina32463@aol.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>64.120.172.225</ip>
      <website>http://asdffsdsdjfhsdjfsdgfsdfd.com/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>Awesome website man, If only I will make something similar by content like that lmao.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="8cfb8ac6-f1cb-4143-a2d1-8369f1b3154b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-10 22:41:00</date>
      <author>fans for you and me</author>
      <email>Litrenta13853@aol.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>5.231.16.144</ip>
      <website>http://asdffsdsdjfhsdjfsdggdfsdfd.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You completed some terrific points there. I have done a search on the party theme and discovered most persons should have the same opinion along with your blog.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d337d023-a17c-4904-962e-5f619aa826d7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-13 07:41:48</date>
      <author>buy facebook fans</author>
      <email>Smetak1186@aol.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>5.231.16.144</ip>
      <website>http://asdffsdsdjfhsdjfsdggdfsdfd.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi, I found your web site in error once i was searching yahoo in this issue, I need to say your posts was in actuality helpful I additionally love the theme, its amazing!. I lack a whole lot a chance to read your entire post presently however have bookmarked it and even add your For. I will be back a week or so. appreciate your an incredible website.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="87ff45e1-7a0a-43cd-8212-0964d4f11812" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-08-20 04:09:40</date>
      <author>Hyon Benoy</author>
      <email>Shoji@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>220.184.95.58</ip>
      <website>http://money.htwlf.com/2014/08/can-you-make-money-with-surveys.html</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>I like what you guys are up also. Such clever work and reporting! Carry on the excellent works guys I have incorporated you guys to my blogroll. I think it&amp;#39;ll improve the value of my website :).</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="61068599-6962-46f8-a262-c8c0d5ae889e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-08-24 15:07:47</date>
      <author>DEBORA Laurence</author>
      <email>annuairesgratuit2009@yahoo.fr</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>90.3.83.185</ip>
      <website>http://www.annuaires-gratuit.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>annuaires-gratuit.com/ vous propose de créer gratuitement un annuaire de sites internet pour un bon référencement.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4c0a0928-6d7b-406e-99ec-bd977a0b6453" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-08-24 18:49:28</date>
      <author>DEBORA Laurence</author>
      <email>annuairesgratuit2009@yahoo.fr</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>90.3.83.185</ip>
      <website>http://www.annuaires-gratuit.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>annuaires-gratuit.com/ vous propose de créer gratuitement un annuaire de sites internet pour un bon référencement.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ce11292b-a466-4b04-ae6e-4de8cf81267e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-20 20:28:50</date>
      <author>DEBORA Laurence</author>
      <email>annuairesgratuit2009@yahoo.fr</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>83.114.107.248</ip>
      <website>http://www.portail2000.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Covoiturage, annonce &amp;amp; covoiturage. Deposer votre annonce gratuitement sur portail2000.com/ et faites des rencontres</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="eb8daee2-b5fc-457d-81a6-4f28620160e4" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-07 13:28:38</date>
      <author>Sharita Shuemaker</author>
      <email>Wearrien99268@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>69.64.48.212</ip>
      <website>http://maxiproxies.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>yeah bookmaking this wasn&amp;#39;t a speculative conclusion great post! . </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ee384b01-3b31-4fa7-a98c-020be2f2b8c5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-08 16:05:19</date>
      <author>idlife</author>
      <email>mike@idlife.cash</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>108.36.200.91</ip>
      <website>http://www.idlife.cash/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice post! Check out my site sometime!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d5b9b6a8-702c-4a70-8859-22f697db0c85" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-09 06:16:01</date>
      <author>Nickolas Condino</author>
      <email>Langland616@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>72.20.36.230</ip>
      <website>http://convivenciacuba.es/intramuros/?p=60</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Lastest &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.skyzone.com.sg&amp;quot;&gt;xxx&amp;lt;/a&gt; best in the best singapore.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6382fe00-d1b1-4c20-82a2-fd1872973aca" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-12 20:32:56</date>
      <author>Cash</author>
      <email>mike@idlife.cash</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>108.36.200.91</ip>
      <website>http://cash.idlife.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice post! I enjoyed reading your post, I have a blog too. Hopefully you can keep your site updated so I can keep reading.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="df622d6c-5675-4e53-82bf-f1b10c50537e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-15 06:54:32</date>
      <author>Mental Health Social Network</author>
      <email>mike@mhsn.co</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>108.36.200.91</ip>
      <website>http://www.mhsn.co/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, nice post!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b74807c6-4742-4c68-8be4-4d38b4e8e8cb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-25 07:44:12</date>
      <author>Irena Foth</author>
      <email>Kimme@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>198.46.139.154</ip>
      <website>http://pcgamecheats2013.blogspot.in/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Oh my goodness! a tremendous article dude. Thanks Nevertheless I am experiencing concern with ur rss . Don’t know why Unable to subscribe to it. Is there anybody getting identical rss drawback? Anyone who knows kindly respond. Thnkx</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>