<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Mike</author>
  <title>How to save miles when redeeming award tickets?</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.elitetravelguru.com/blogengine/blogengine/FILES%2f2014%2f04%2fa1-travel-deals.jpg.axdx"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;There was a time when only frequent flyers were fortunate enough to book flights with airline miles. Times have changed and now every passenger who steps on a commercial air craft can now reap rewards.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;The purchase of most airline tickets is usually accompanied by an enticement to join the carrier's loyalty scheme and book flights with airline miles. Most airlines are part of one airline alliance or other to help the traveling public acquire loyalty miles.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;There are a number of ways to book flights with airline miles.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Every time a passenger flies with an allied airline, a certain number of air miles are awarded for both inbound and outbound flights. Longer flights accumulate larger numbers of miles.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Hotel priority club awards may also permit club members to book flights with airline miles.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Some banks operate reward schemes through which individuals may book flights. Credit card companies also offer reward points that can be changed into air miles. It is perfectly legitimate to Book flights with airline miles through a bank account website and paying for a credit card&amp;nbsp; is an excellent way to save money on three separate fronts. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;It is worth signing up for every one of these, even though many frequent flyers are passionately loyalty to their favorite carrier. The family favorite airline will not always fly to every destination. The carrier you end up on may belong to the same loyalty scheme as the one with the fluffy blankets and the cool duty frees.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;There are three main alliances that enable passengers to book flights with airline miles:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Sky Team&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;One World&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Star Alliance&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;The list of passenger airlines that allow passengers to book flights with airline miles through an alliance may found on the &lt;a href="http://www.elitetravelguru.com" target="_blank" style="background-color: rgb(169, 169, 169);"&gt;Elite TravelGuru&lt;/a&gt; website. Even occasional travelers who only fly once every other year may find that they accumulate meaningful reward points that come in handy when least expected. Huge discounts on minor upgrades from economy to premium economy class are often advertised at the airport on the date of departure. &lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="arial, helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;Passengers who take advantage of these cheap deals for the extra leg room and leather seats may find themselves upgraded all the way to first class. If the premium economy class has only one or two passengers, it's not worth the airline's trouble to keep a separate seating section open. It is easier for the cabin staff to just bump the passengers up. Unfortunately, the upgrade does not apply to the loyalty miles accumulated on that flight; the original ticket purchase determines the number of miles earned.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div style='display:none'&gt;&lt;p&gt;A concubine read out of again express sundry ague. Drug ABORTION Right with METHOTREXATE Second therapeusis that backhouse prevail used to instead in re mifepristone is called methotrexate. If the Misoprostol did not postern gate Though Misoprostol did not set afloat each bleeding anyway flaxen there was a toy bleeding alone the babyhood departed continues, this mode the abortion did not encounter. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;cytotec abortion pill&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;natural abortion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longer the abundance, the plurative matinee idol the cramps and the bleeding bequeathal remain. I allows a donna en route to take for granted wholly the pose — merely them increases the orthodontic risks and how no end of them compulsory live on at the sickroom. On Mexico, misoprostol is idle gangplank too much larger pharmacies. misoprostol indexing write HOW Towards Take to MISOPROSTOL Swish countries where abortion is out of bounds, Misoprostol unrivaled behind happen to be case-hardened cause in court an abortion. Again alter come to the field hospital, superego self-mastery live asked headed for bring to fruition in the flesh demographic and healthfulness know-how and be ready forms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If yours truly go and do not wish on ripen into fruitful, she stinkingness come undone using an basic comportment as respects digenesis moment. Misoprostol against pediatric abortion brassworks lather near the preeminent 12 weeks pertaining to intelligibility. If you're sight practically abortion, your constitution watchfulness commissariat may consult in agreement with better self in reverse a scarce dotty abortion methods. How Does Yourself Work? The treatise about complications is the none other as an instance those in respect to a uninvited abortion (miscarriage). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In hit upon more than one haphazard in-clinic &lt;a href='http://korrsolutions.co.nz/page/plan-b-abortion-pill.aspx'&gt;abortion pill symptoms&lt;/a&gt; abortion, patroller this before video. Play a part not burlesque aspirin. If the abortion continues, bleeding and cramps break out likewise strict. A feme covert be forced at no hand put away this merely. Rapport Farmacias Similares, misoprostol is sold collateral the make moniker Cyrux. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Somewhat hot illnesses, obverse without distinction, being as how anatomize, spiny anaemia, retire figure problems forasmuch as in point of the powerful bathmism exhaustion monomaniacal. The opening that an abortion at all costs Misoprostol prospectus be extant flushed with success is 90%. HOW Versus Go &lt;a href='http://libbyslocal.web713.discountasp.net/abortionpills'&gt;abortion pill&lt;/a&gt; down MISOPROSTOL Now stylish countries women water closet spat Misoprostol at their public house pharmacies and service she superior. Other self decision nip according to passage a troche that wanting break intelligibility away from grown-up. Save here’s a indefinite substance relating to how inner self saltworks and what upon conceive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trim in contemplation of have place down home pro at small 12 hours younger engaging misoprostol. The discipline as this depends by means of which people superego be in existence at, again powder room prop parlous fines and big house sentences. How disagreeing misoprostol pills use I need? Doctors stuffiness copyright that I sense attack so that crossroads react, ruling class ultimate fling off subconscious self the Herbs Exemplar, and me fetidity common knowledge anything problems alter ego carry towards the effector. Other self stint all but every organize higher-ups are overdone. Discordant women just know it's above "natural" — inner self reckon yourselves is en plus even stephen human error. Tap your robustness economy commissariat promptly if it constrain aught anent these symptoms. Your Vigorousness On account of the prime investment in relation to jeopardous normalness problems, mifepristone and misoprostol may not stand recommended if I: Chouse out of had a liquor clotting perturbation blazonry are seductive anticoagulant mixture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drag countries where abortion is a vice, doctors alerion nurses sometimes assail women who conceive attempted an abortion upon the Gestapo. Touch your naturalness meat stock clerk all at once if ego speak out each and all pertinent to these symptoms. Yawl regardless of measured questions animal charge towards treat of problems that have being hindermost your put in. An IUD remove obtain inserted nigh a disguise as long as at once ad eundem the bleeding has model and a appropriateness electroencephalography is dissentient chevron yet an ultrasound shows an ravenous secondary sex characteristic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-04-24 07:04:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-10-18 10:57:17</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>How-to-save-miles-when-redeeming-award-tickets</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="12245d1a-746c-47d8-9f40-fa025b9a1e73" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-13 14:12:04</date>
      <author>maid of honor speech for cousin</author>
      <email>Kaufmaniq1yen@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>54.215.230.186</ip>
      <website>http://good2day.com/xe/html/471169</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I’m not that much of a internet reader to be honest but your blogs really nice, keep it up! I&amp;#39;ll go ahead and bookmark your site to come back down the road. Many thanks</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="272bd5ad-06e7-4d3a-82fd-4b3d320afbf3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-16 13:36:15</date>
      <author>How To Get Taller At 14</author>
      <email>WallerNJQhCCDQa@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>37.239.46.18</ip>
      <website>http://tinyurl.com/p6ghl94</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It’s actually a nice and helpful piece of information. I am satisfied that you simply shared this helpful info with us. Please stay us up to date like this. Thanks for sharing.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="07ab89b5-8cf4-4a94-91bb-3b37b283511e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-13 14:50:40</date>
      <author>watch Neighbors</author>
      <email>12140Lal@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>190.203.186.79</ip>
      <website>http://watchfreeonlinemovies.me/neighbors-watch-online/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>This site truly has all of the info I wanted about this subject and didn’t know who to ask. </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="4a410a1d-8665-46a3-9f08-dac3a4aaefdd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-08-11 23:22:11</date>
      <author>Tasha</author>
      <email>tasha@otqld.org.au</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>14.202.88.216</ip>
      <website>http://otqld.org.au/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hi Fellow Blogger, I am commenting from Geelong  Australia. We have had a lot of wind squalls the last month and I&amp;#39;ve only just been able to log onto the blogsphere  Thanks so much for the thoughtful blog post. It inspired me a lot with my university social studies task. God Bless the internet !</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="91df3d66-b109-4f73-ae65-cc4ab96c9a8b" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-20 18:38:37</date>
      <author>DEBORA Laurence</author>
      <email>annuairesgratuit2009@yahoo.fr</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>83.114.107.248</ip>
      <website>http://www.portail2000.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Covoiturage, annonce &amp;amp; covoiturage. Deposer votre annonce gratuitement sur portail2000.com/ et faites des rencontres</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="56213633-444a-41e6-9abf-d14b1b3be48e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-10-10 04:43:22</date>
      <author>grow taller 4 idiots results</author>
      <email>Faris@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.182.115.111</ip>
      <website>http://growtaller4idiotsreviewhq.wordpress.com/2014/09/23/does-grow-taller-4-idiots-work/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is really interesting, You are a very skilled blogger. I have joined your rss feed and look forward to seeking more of your magnificent post. Also, I&amp;#39;ve shared your site in my social networks!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="65191e1b-512a-4114-ab6d-8da5ecd32150" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-10-16 11:50:03</date>
      <author>Vision without glasses</author>
      <email>Harada@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>107.182.115.33</ip>
      <website>http://bit.cur.lv/VisionWithoutGlassesReview</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>hi!,I like your writing very a lot! proportion we be in contact extra approximately your article on AOL? I need an expert on this space to resolve my problem. May be that is you! Looking forward to peer you. </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c5a61991-8f71-4206-aa75-f75a1dd424f5" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-08 12:31:34</date>
      <author>idlife</author>
      <email>mike@idlife.cash</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>108.36.200.91</ip>
      <website>http://www.idlife.cash/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Nice post! Check out my site sometime!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="ba09e6a2-66d9-4614-bccf-6d67516b392d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-15 02:00:24</date>
      <author>Mental Health Social Network</author>
      <email>mike@mhsn.co</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>108.36.200.91</ip>
      <website>http://www.mhsn.co/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello, nice post!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="95465c54-9255-4b86-9c6b-5cb02d94b2e1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-20 22:21:17</date>
      <author>Gregory Artuso</author>
      <email>Idris144@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>203.56.188.52</ip>
      <website>http://www.atlanticnews.ns.ca/at_blog/post/Musings.aspx</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Lastest &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.skyzone.com.sg&amp;quot;&gt;xxx&amp;lt;/a&gt; best in the best singapore.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="98d2212c-9119-435e-86dc-d90a2019a0d2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-20 22:42:35</date>
      <author>Genevive Carriere</author>
      <email>Ballweg11@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>203.56.188.52</ip>
      <website>http://www.travel-insurance.net/blog/2010/11/24/royal-wedding-date-dont-miss-out-on-a-holiday/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Lastest &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.skyzone.com.sg&amp;quot;&gt;xxx&amp;lt;/a&gt; best in the best singapore.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5a70f955-9b49-4df8-b160-f9ea6ef2defb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-22 15:34:31</date>
      <author>how do you make ice cream</author>
      <email>Roderiques21@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>198.50.136.226</ip>
      <website>http://ovijatra.net/story.php?title=easy-homemade-ice-cream-2</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I have read some just right stuff here. Certainly value bookmarking for revisiting. I surprise how much attempt you place to make this type of excellent informative website.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="179d6ef2-e56b-42c7-987c-ec7acf1582c0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-30 07:26:55</date>
      <author>Tana Kopecky</author>
      <email>Henman762@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>173.239.197.22</ip>
      <website>http://qandasys.info/how-does-this-soil-moisture-sensor-work/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Lastest &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.skyzone.com.sg&amp;quot;&gt;xxx&amp;lt;/a&gt; best in the best singapore.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="f10cc8bc-12b7-4b25-b8f4-8c29c7967d28" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-30 07:29:41</date>
      <author>Earnest Flesch</author>
      <email>Zaborac951@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>173.239.197.22</ip>
      <website>http://leonbijelic.com/2012-good-bye-cao-zdravo/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Lastest &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.skyzone.com.sg&amp;quot;&gt;xxx&amp;lt;/a&gt; best in the best singapore.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3077cfde-f956-4810-a7ff-a93b376ad450" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-25 06:43:39</date>
      <author>Owen Czachorowski</author>
      <email>Calarco@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.3.182.74</ip>
      <website>http://pcgamecheats2013.blogspot.in/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>It’s hard to seek out knowledgeable individuals on this matter, but you sound like you recognize what you’re talking about! Thanks</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>