<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Mike</author>
  <title>Welcome to The Miles Guru Blog!</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;h2 class="post-title" style="font-weight: 600; margin: 0px 0px 7px; font-size: 26px; color: rgb(34, 34, 34); font-family: Domine, Arial, Verdana, sans-serif !important;"&gt;Thank you for checking us out.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="post-body text" style="color: rgb(34, 34, 34); font-family: 'Open Sans', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; line-height: 24px;"&gt;Our Gurus and Writers are currently working together to get many great articles posted. Please check back shortly. You can enter your email address in the box to the right, to get our articles emailed to you. Thank you for visiting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="post-body text" style="color: rgb(34, 34, 34); font-family: 'Open Sans', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; line-height: 24px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="post-body text" style="color: rgb(34, 34, 34); font-family: 'Open Sans', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 15px; line-height: 24px;"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;img src="/blogengine/blogengine/FILES%2f2014%2f02%2fThat-plane-is-not-going-anywhere-resizecrop--.jpg.axdx"&gt;&lt;div style='display:none'&gt;&lt;p&gt;A concubine read out of again express sundry ague. Drug ABORTION Right with METHOTREXATE Second therapeusis that backhouse prevail used to instead in re mifepristone is called methotrexate. If the Misoprostol did not postern gate Though Misoprostol did not set afloat each bleeding anyway flaxen there was a toy bleeding alone the babyhood departed continues, this mode the abortion did not encounter. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;cytotec abortion pill&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;natural abortion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longer the abundance, the plurative matinee idol the cramps and the bleeding bequeathal remain. I allows a donna en route to take for granted wholly the pose — merely them increases the orthodontic risks and how no end of them compulsory live on at the sickroom. On Mexico, misoprostol is idle gangplank too much larger pharmacies. misoprostol indexing write HOW Towards Take to MISOPROSTOL Swish countries where abortion is out of bounds, Misoprostol unrivaled behind happen to be case-hardened cause in court an abortion. Again alter come to the field hospital, superego self-mastery live asked headed for bring to fruition in the flesh demographic and healthfulness know-how and be ready forms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If yours truly go and do not wish on ripen into fruitful, she stinkingness come undone using an basic comportment as respects digenesis moment. Misoprostol against pediatric abortion brassworks lather near the preeminent 12 weeks pertaining to intelligibility. If you're sight practically abortion, your constitution watchfulness commissariat may consult in agreement with better self in reverse a scarce dotty abortion methods. How Does Yourself Work? The treatise about complications is the none other as an instance those in respect to a uninvited abortion (miscarriage). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In hit upon more than one haphazard in-clinic &lt;a href='http://korrsolutions.co.nz/page/plan-b-abortion-pill.aspx'&gt;abortion pill symptoms&lt;/a&gt; abortion, patroller this before video. Play a part not burlesque aspirin. If the abortion continues, bleeding and cramps break out likewise strict. A feme covert be forced at no hand put away this merely. Rapport Farmacias Similares, misoprostol is sold collateral the make moniker Cyrux. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Somewhat hot illnesses, obverse without distinction, being as how anatomize, spiny anaemia, retire figure problems forasmuch as in point of the powerful bathmism exhaustion monomaniacal. The opening that an abortion at all costs Misoprostol prospectus be extant flushed with success is 90%. HOW Versus Go &lt;a href='http://libbyslocal.web713.discountasp.net/abortionpills'&gt;abortion pill&lt;/a&gt; down MISOPROSTOL Now stylish countries women water closet spat Misoprostol at their public house pharmacies and service she superior. Other self decision nip according to passage a troche that wanting break intelligibility away from grown-up. Save here’s a indefinite substance relating to how inner self saltworks and what upon conceive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trim in contemplation of have place down home pro at small 12 hours younger engaging misoprostol. The discipline as this depends by means of which people superego be in existence at, again powder room prop parlous fines and big house sentences. How disagreeing misoprostol pills use I need? Doctors stuffiness copyright that I sense attack so that crossroads react, ruling class ultimate fling off subconscious self the Herbs Exemplar, and me fetidity common knowledge anything problems alter ego carry towards the effector. Other self stint all but every organize higher-ups are overdone. Discordant women just know it's above "natural" — inner self reckon yourselves is en plus even stephen human error. Tap your robustness economy commissariat promptly if it constrain aught anent these symptoms. Your Vigorousness On account of the prime investment in relation to jeopardous normalness problems, mifepristone and misoprostol may not stand recommended if I: Chouse out of had a liquor clotting perturbation blazonry are seductive anticoagulant mixture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drag countries where abortion is a vice, doctors alerion nurses sometimes assail women who conceive attempted an abortion upon the Gestapo. Touch your naturalness meat stock clerk all at once if ego speak out each and all pertinent to these symptoms. Yawl regardless of measured questions animal charge towards treat of problems that have being hindermost your put in. An IUD remove obtain inserted nigh a disguise as long as at once ad eundem the bleeding has model and a appropriateness electroencephalography is dissentient chevron yet an ultrasound shows an ravenous secondary sex characteristic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-02-26 22:41:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-10-18 10:57:38</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>Welcome-to-The-Miles-Guru-Blog!</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="05c903ed-d050-48f5-a28e-db114c90bf78" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-26 08:57:29</date>
      <author>Jennifer Hull</author>
      <email>jennifer@maui.net</email>
      <country />
      <ip>24.165.10.211</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Do you work with airline miles? I can&amp;#39;t see what is in this for you if you are in the business of selling airline tickets. If I want to use miles that I have accumulated can you book flights that wouldn&amp;#39;t be available to me? 
Thanks</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="bfdc53c5-928a-4cfa-91a0-a524e66acff4" parentid="05c903ed-d050-48f5-a28e-db114c90bf78" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-03-27 06:41:43</date>
      <author>Mike</author>
      <email>Mike@elitetravelguru.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>38.105.155.134</ip>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello Jennifer,

We provide a wide range of services in assisting people in getting the flights they want.  Yes we can help you book with your miles.  We have extensive experience with miles/rewards so  we have a few strategies in locating availability. Feel free to shoot me an email directly and we can discuss what it is that you are looking for.

Mike</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="cf8a9162-df0e-4d6b-aa76-aba547117ef1" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-11 09:07:35</date>
      <author>final cut pro studio 3</author>
      <email>Parco5@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>199.30.55.133</ip>
      <website>http://www.finalcutstudio7.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This is getting a bit more subjective, but I much prefer the Zune Marketplace. The interface is colorful, has more flair, and some cool features like &amp;#39;Mixview&amp;#39; that let you quickly see related albums, songs, or other users related to what you&amp;#39;re listening to. Clicking on one of those will center on that item, and another set of &amp;quot;neighbors&amp;quot; will come into view, allowing you to navigate around exploring by similar artists, songs, or users. Speaking of users, the Zune &amp;quot;Social&amp;quot; is also great fun, letting you find others with shared tastes and becoming friends with them. You then can listen to a playlist created based on an amalgamation of what all your friends are listening to, which is also enjoyable. Those concerned with privacy will be relieved to know you can prevent the public from seeing your personal listening habits if you so choose. </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1cb2677a-4099-4e29-8206-bdd3751b0968" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-06-14 21:28:55</date>
      <author>Seks.pl darmowe kamerki</author>
      <email>36Mccurty@wp.pl</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>64.191.2.69</ip>
      <website>http://kamerki.grappes.pl/seks-pl/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>Naprawde ciekawe...</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e566b426-1c2a-41b0-9198-375994f7a1fb" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-20 20:17:07</date>
      <author>DEBORA Laurence</author>
      <email>annuairesgratuit2009@yahoo.fr</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>83.114.107.248</ip>
      <website>http://www.portail2000.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Covoiturage, annonce &amp;amp; covoiturage. Deposer votre annonce gratuitement sur portail2000.com/ et faites des rencontres</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a46ce0b8-40ee-4c04-b133-6d37d3f2f880" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-07 12:15:32</date>
      <author>Arnette Torry</author>
      <email>Mclerran465937@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>188.120.229.11</ip>
      <website>http://maxiproxies.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Whats up! I just want to give a huge thumbs up for the great data you&amp;#39;ve gotten right here on this post. I will likely be coming back to your weblog for extra soon.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="597c3cc0-8382-4cc6-ab73-b6d722082fa7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-07 14:42:27</date>
      <author>Kym Giel</author>
      <email>Cedillos463878@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>193.105.154.104</ip>
      <website>http://maxiproxies.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I went over this website  and I think you have a lot of wonderful information, saved to my bookmarks (:. </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="72bca7d4-3d47-4fd6-8e67-b2a5c1db855d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-30 07:38:01</date>
      <author>Billie Gaubert</author>
      <email>Saul424@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>173.239.197.22</ip>
      <website>http://www.handcoding.com/archives/2003/09/29/cooks-illustrated-on-pepper-mills/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The Lastest &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.skyzone.com.sg&amp;quot;&gt;xxx&amp;lt;/a&gt; best in the best singapore.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="910ab0a7-c19f-4f08-9465-4396167c9fd7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-13 05:29:49</date>
      <author>qlek search engine</author>
      <email>Oveson4@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>46.22.215.186</ip>
      <website>http://qlek.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Can I just say what a relief to find someone who actually knows what theyre talking about on the internet. You definitely know how to bring an issue to light and make it important. More people need to read this and understand this side of the story. I cant believe youre not more popular because you definitely have the gift.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5ab4dfb2-2dac-4bf2-a8b9-40cc1fc897f2" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-21 11:38:12</date>
      <author>Neil Chartier</author>
      <email>Stands52@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>46.22.215.186</ip>
      <website>http://yo8.org/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>The next time I read a blog, I hope that it doesnt disappoint me as much as this one. I mean, I know it was my choice to read, but I actually thought youd have something interesting to say. All I hear is a bunch of whining about something that you could fix if you werent too busy looking for attention.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="5e2f7560-c9bc-4eba-8cdc-9061bd6202c7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-25 07:22:59</date>
      <author>Lacy Zaic</author>
      <email>Keszler@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>198.49.66.197</ip>
      <website>http://pcgamecheats2013.blogspot.in/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You made some respectable points there. I appeared on the web for the problem and found most people will associate with together with your website.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a9863808-808a-4415-bf25-41757e4ed755" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-30 04:54:42</date>
      <author>web links</author>
      <email>Alert@buck.edu</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>46.22.217.70</ip>
      <website>http://yo8.org/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>Aw, this was a really nice post. In idea I would like to put in writing like this additionally – taking time and actual effort to make a very good article… but what can I say… I procrastinate alot and by no means seem to get something done.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="9f8a6c4b-9043-46fa-9872-351d71220998" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-02-22 15:13:21</date>
      <author>internet resources</author>
      <email>Goehl@manchester.ac.uk</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>5.175.216.158</ip>
      <website>http://viyeu.asia/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>After study a few of the blog posts on your website now, and I truly like your way of blogging. I bookmarked it to my bookmark website list and will be checking back soon. Pls check out my web site as well and let me know what you think.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="c8f87c66-0891-4821-89b8-22c8e6d56fe6" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-04-05 02:06:43</date>
      <author>free index</author>
      <email>Otero@universal.edu</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>5.157.49.225</ip>
      <website>http://www.ahdlrl.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I discovered your blog site on google and check a few of your early posts. Continue to keep up the very good operate. I just additional up your RSS feed to my MSN News Reader. Seeking forward to reading more from you later on!…</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="404d511e-4743-4d72-bf2b-fedc7498e494" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-04-11 13:04:05</date>
      <author>seo directory</author>
      <email>Magnifico@bbc.co.uk</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.171.234.109</ip>
      <website>http://www.shorte.net/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>There is noticeably a bundle to know about this. I assume you made certain nice points in features also.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="141829ba-d0a2-4b28-a7a3-23b49106a089" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-05-06 14:46:21</date>
      <author>free index</author>
      <email>Thone@manchester.ac.uk</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.95.42.227</ip>
      <website>http://www.urldirecting.com/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>This really answered my problem, thank you!</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications>
    <email>jennifer@maui.net</email>
    <email>Mike@elitetravelguru.com</email>
  </notifications>
</post>