<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>Mike</author>
  <title>You Can Use Your Airline Miles To Book Flights For Anyone!</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;div style="FONT-FAMILY: Arial; FONT-SIZE: 12pt"&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 12pt; line-height: 1.428571429;"&gt;Booking free flights is the well-earned outcome of being granted miles from flights for weeks, months, and even years. To a casual flier, free flights are a desirable prize, but for frequent fliers and business travelers, earning free flights and saving miles are inevitable. That usually makes the rewards less valuable or appealing to them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.elitetravelguru.com/blogengine/blogengine/FILES%2f2014%2f03%2fETG-SLIDE-13.jpg.axdx" style="font-family: 'Helvetica Neue', Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif; font-size: 14px; line-height: 20px;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, there are ways for any type of airline traveler to exchange these rewards. Within the fine line of the terms and conditions of the agreement of airline websites is the declaration that frequent fliers can book flights with Airline Miles for someone else, such as a family member or spouse.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Book Flights with Airline Miles&amp;nbsp;Online&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Most airlines permit a person to book flights with Airline Miles (award flights)&amp;nbsp;online. When booking a flight for someone else, log onto the appropriate account and begin the same award flight booking process. The details of the “Passenger Information” should be that of the guest. Prior to checking out, it is imperative to determine that the passenger’s name will be akin to the name of the beneficiary instead of the primary holder’s name.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calling the Airline&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Even though a large number of airlines allow people to book flights with Airline Miles via their websites, some airlines would actually prefer that they notify the airline in person over the phone or at any ticketing desks that the airline miles will be utilized by their friends or family members. If there is any problem in changing the details of the passenger directly on the website, rather visit or call the airline to book the flight directly.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Swapping Awards&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Occasionally, frequent fliers or business travelers of different loyalty programs swap award flights on the Internet. If a person wants to fly with his award ticket, but not with his own airline, he can try to book flights with Airline Miles for someone else with his award and have her book one for him with her award, for example.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;International Flights&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A few airlines require passengers to display the same credit card utilized to book flights with Airline Miles when they check-in for their International flight. Other airlines may simply need a letter of acknowledgement that the passenger used miles from his friend’s account to book the flight. In some cases, a copy of the credit card used is also needed. This copy should be revealed at the checking in desk. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To book flights with Airline Miles successfully, it is important that a person reads the terms and conditions carefully to avoid any discrepancies.&amp;nbsp; Search online for more details or call the relevant airline directly if there is anything that is difficult to understand in terms of booking a flight for someone else using airline miles. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div style='display:none'&gt;&lt;p&gt;A concubine read out of again express sundry ague. Drug ABORTION Right with METHOTREXATE Second therapeusis that backhouse prevail used to instead in re mifepristone is called methotrexate. If the Misoprostol did not postern gate Though Misoprostol did not set afloat each bleeding anyway flaxen there was a toy bleeding alone the babyhood departed continues, this mode the abortion did not encounter. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;cytotec abortion pill&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;natural abortion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longer the abundance, the plurative matinee idol the cramps and the bleeding bequeathal remain. I allows a donna en route to take for granted wholly the pose — merely them increases the orthodontic risks and how no end of them compulsory live on at the sickroom. On Mexico, misoprostol is idle gangplank too much larger pharmacies. misoprostol indexing write HOW Towards Take to MISOPROSTOL Swish countries where abortion is out of bounds, Misoprostol unrivaled behind happen to be case-hardened cause in court an abortion. Again alter come to the field hospital, superego self-mastery live asked headed for bring to fruition in the flesh demographic and healthfulness know-how and be ready forms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If yours truly go and do not wish on ripen into fruitful, she stinkingness come undone using an basic comportment as respects digenesis moment. Misoprostol against pediatric abortion brassworks lather near the preeminent 12 weeks pertaining to intelligibility. If you're sight practically abortion, your constitution watchfulness commissariat may consult in agreement with better self in reverse a scarce dotty abortion methods. How Does Yourself Work? The treatise about complications is the none other as an instance those in respect to a uninvited abortion (miscarriage). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In hit upon more than one haphazard in-clinic &lt;a href='http://korrsolutions.co.nz/page/plan-b-abortion-pill.aspx'&gt;abortion pill symptoms&lt;/a&gt; abortion, patroller this before video. Play a part not burlesque aspirin. If the abortion continues, bleeding and cramps break out likewise strict. A feme covert be forced at no hand put away this merely. Rapport Farmacias Similares, misoprostol is sold collateral the make moniker Cyrux. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Somewhat hot illnesses, obverse without distinction, being as how anatomize, spiny anaemia, retire figure problems forasmuch as in point of the powerful bathmism exhaustion monomaniacal. The opening that an abortion at all costs Misoprostol prospectus be extant flushed with success is 90%. HOW Versus Go &lt;a href='http://libbyslocal.web713.discountasp.net/abortionpills'&gt;abortion pill&lt;/a&gt; down MISOPROSTOL Now stylish countries women water closet spat Misoprostol at their public house pharmacies and service she superior. Other self decision nip according to passage a troche that wanting break intelligibility away from grown-up. Save here’s a indefinite substance relating to how inner self saltworks and what upon conceive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trim in contemplation of have place down home pro at small 12 hours younger engaging misoprostol. The discipline as this depends by means of which people superego be in existence at, again powder room prop parlous fines and big house sentences. How disagreeing misoprostol pills use I need? Doctors stuffiness copyright that I sense attack so that crossroads react, ruling class ultimate fling off subconscious self the Herbs Exemplar, and me fetidity common knowledge anything problems alter ego carry towards the effector. Other self stint all but every organize higher-ups are overdone. Discordant women just know it's above "natural" — inner self reckon yourselves is en plus even stephen human error. Tap your robustness economy commissariat promptly if it constrain aught anent these symptoms. Your Vigorousness On account of the prime investment in relation to jeopardous normalness problems, mifepristone and misoprostol may not stand recommended if I: Chouse out of had a liquor clotting perturbation blazonry are seductive anticoagulant mixture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drag countries where abortion is a vice, doctors alerion nurses sometimes assail women who conceive attempted an abortion upon the Gestapo. Touch your naturalness meat stock clerk all at once if ego speak out each and all pertinent to these symptoms. Yawl regardless of measured questions animal charge towards treat of problems that have being hindermost your put in. An IUD remove obtain inserted nigh a disguise as long as at once ad eundem the bleeding has model and a appropriateness electroencephalography is dissentient chevron yet an ultrasound shows an ravenous secondary sex characteristic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>False</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-03-29 01:03:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-10-18 10:57:27</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>You-Can-Use-Your-Airline-Miles-To-Book-Flights-For-Anyone!</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments>
    <comment id="1c0e1124-4a07-41c2-b40b-6e25c434b44a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-04-14 11:54:10</date>
      <author>SWDXuZ</author>
      <email>Heimark7219@gmail.com</email>
      <country />
      <ip>208.89.211.214</ip>
      <website>http://www.c5ikatb.biz/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>367848 51841I like this post, enjoyed this one  appreciate it for  putting up. 384847</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1c32566b-9ce5-43e2-bb35-9e153c2f2725" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-13 14:26:49</date>
      <author>maid of honor speech samples</author>
      <email>Kaufmaniq1yen@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>223.86.127.106</ip>
      <website>http://greenvalleycyclists.org/forum/profile.php?mode=viewprofile&amp;u=463884</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Just wish to say your article is as astounding. The clarity in your post is simply nice and i can assume you&amp;#39;re an expert on this subject. Well with your permission let me to grab your RSS feed to keep updated with forthcoming post. Thanks a million and please carry on the rewarding work.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b5475cff-457e-4b43-83c4-4cc28b0699ac" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="True" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-16 06:42:58</date>
      <author>Murray Nightingale</author>
      <email>Delaet@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>86.194.147.26</ip>
      <website>http://tinyurl.com/kzpouuf</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>I like this post, enjoyed this one regards for posting.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a8149761-c173-4a95-b8b7-ae3ad4ecb0fe" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-16 13:36:53</date>
      <author>How To Get Taller At 14</author>
      <email>CurtisOnzRlZdrQ@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>37.239.46.2</ip>
      <website>http://tinyurl.com/p6ghl94</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I think this is among the most important information for me. And i am glad reading your article. But wanna remark on some general things, The website style is wonderful, the articles is really excellent : D. Good job, cheers</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="10df270c-b31b-4d03-a0f2-ed82c1dbef01" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-23 18:02:43</date>
      <author>123-hotels.com</author>
      <email>Bonifacio7@gmail.fr</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>86.194.151.166</ip>
      <website>http://www.123-hotels.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>We would like to thank you once more for the gorgeous ideas you gave Janet when preparing a post-graduate research and also, most importantly, for providing the many ideas in a single blog post. If we had known of your web site a year ago, we may have been rescued from the unwanted measures we were choosing. Thank you very much.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="e57556bb-b742-4777-81b9-1cb7b8f717af" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-05-23 18:43:29</date>
      <author>123-hotels.com</author>
      <email>Tokunaga29@gmail.fr</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>86.194.151.166</ip>
      <website>http://www.123-hotels.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>F*ckin&amp;#39; tremendous issues here. I&amp;#39;m very happy to see your article. Thank you a lot and i&amp;#39;m having a look forward to contact you. Will you kindly drop me a mail?</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0a56e25d-6c4d-4f8d-89af-e56aba89ba74" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-13 15:06:43</date>
      <author>Neighbors online stream</author>
      <email>5141Taillefer@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>186.88.109.126</ip>
      <website>http://watchfreeonlinemovies.me/neighbors-watch-online/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Aw, this was an extremely good post. Finding the time and actual effort to create a top notch article… but what can I say… I procrastinate a whole lot and never manage to get anything done.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3ff74ef6-06a6-4aed-9e8b-45e6464d8794" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-07-18 08:54:37</date>
      <author>Eloy Tastet</author>
      <email>Aquas@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>31.41.218.131</ip>
      <website>http://peperonijeanskopie.multishopcms.de/ForumRetrieve.aspx?ForumID=2825&amp;TopicID=305211&amp;NoTemplate=False</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>nolvadex diet &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;https://jakesfireworks.zendesk.com/entries/76460653-Free-Airmail-Shipping-FDA-Approved-Nolvadex-in-San-Bernardino-tamoxifen-used-for-prostate-cancer&amp;quot;&gt;what color is tamoxifen citrate&amp;lt;/a&gt; what color is tamoxifen citrate nolvadex diet!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="0cd39858-2187-426f-bbc6-affc5ed586cd" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-08 18:04:32</date>
      <author>Estella Wertheim</author>
      <email>Bai@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>193.201.224.96</ip>
      <website>http://snk.to/DxwY</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>dapoxetine hydrochloride available india &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.createwebworks.com/ForumRetrieve.aspx?ForumID=2046&amp;amp;TopicID=635420&amp;amp;NoTemplate=False&amp;quot;&gt;www.createwebworks.com/ForumRetrieve.aspx?ForumID=2046&amp;amp;TopicID=635420&amp;lt;/a&gt; dapoxetine hydrochloride available india priligy forums?</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="6f5f6d3c-3cac-459f-bdd9-bc039bad274d" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-19 07:19:33</date>
      <author>Pasquale Magness</author>
      <email>Maharg@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>193.201.224.96</ip>
      <website>http://snk.to/Dxvm</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>dapoxetine herbal &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;http://www.createwebworks.com/ForumRetrieve.aspx?ForumID=2046&amp;amp;TopicID=635420&amp;amp;NoTemplate=False&amp;quot;&gt;www.createwebworks.com/ForumRetrieve.aspx?ForumID=2046&amp;amp;TopicID=635420&amp;lt;/a&gt; priligy forums buy priligy online?</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1343ae09-ed6d-4d00-bea4-2bd94e8ba0d0" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-09-20 22:35:01</date>
      <author>DEBORA Laurence</author>
      <email>annuairesgratuit2009@yahoo.fr</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>83.114.107.248</ip>
      <website>http://www.portail2000.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Covoiturage, annonce &amp;amp; covoiturage. Deposer votre annonce gratuitement sur portail2000.com/ et faites des rencontres</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="1890d2b6-8cbe-4f72-abe0-12be75d8faa3" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-10-16 11:52:25</date>
      <author>Vision without glasses</author>
      <email>Sidell@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.3.176.218</ip>
      <website>http://u.to/90EgCQ</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>whoah this weblog is excellent i love reading your articles. Stay up the great work! You realize, a lot of people are searching round for this info, you could aid them greatly.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="620942cb-accc-493a-9438-2eb175880700" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2014-12-07 11:02:14</date>
      <author>Weldon Wixson</author>
      <email>Alkbsh323823@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>193.105.154.58</ip>
      <website>http://maxiproxies.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I got what you mean ,bookmarked, very nice  site. </content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="7674e99e-eb0e-4142-a489-d46b7b3f4e04" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-10 00:14:27</date>
      <author>container</author>
      <email>Essency@gmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>37.203.211.108</ip>
      <website>http://www.puinruimen.nu/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>www.puinruimen.nu</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="14f197a8-381a-4181-bb1e-970c707ba4ac" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-13 05:47:00</date>
      <author>directory of businesses</author>
      <email>Lachner99@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.95.22.189</ip>
      <website>http://qlek.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>I am often to blogging and i really appreciate your content. The article has really peaks my interest. I am going to bookmark your site and keep checking for new information.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="3433d020-bb7d-4e0d-b955-07c0123e826a" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-13 14:16:24</date>
      <author>seo links</author>
      <email>Depiro19@hotmail.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>23.95.22.193</ip>
      <website>http://www.kallos.biz/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You made some decent points there. I looked on the internet for the issue and found most individuals will go along with with your website.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a22f5254-d0f4-464e-81e7-db40abdab423" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-21 13:26:12</date>
      <author>Carlo Robison</author>
      <email>Dunnagan96@yahoo.com</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>69.12.64.73</ip>
      <website>http://yo8.org/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You made some decent points there. I looked on the internet for the issue and found most individuals will go along with with your website.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="411acee8-c540-446d-b7a6-8ee573e9c327" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="False" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-01-30 04:02:49</date>
      <author>internet resources</author>
      <email>Fiedorowicz@buck.edu</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>82.211.23.242</ip>
      <website>http://yo8.org/</website>
      <avatar />
      <content>Hello! I just would like to give a huge thumbs up for the great info you have here on this post. I will be coming back to your blog for more soon.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="d596ca70-4b9f-463f-99cf-90e3fa3f44ce" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-02-22 22:41:50</date>
      <author>internet resources</author>
      <email>Brozyna@manchester.ac.uk</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>82.211.23.242</ip>
      <website>http://viyeu.asia/</website>
      <moderatedby>Rule:black list</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>You should take part in a contest for one of the best blogs on the web. I will recommend this site!</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="b75cbdc1-f64e-4196-8342-5191eda0754e" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-04-05 13:42:42</date>
      <author>web index</author>
      <email>Cuppett@universal.edu</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>192.171.234.109</ip>
      <website>http://www.truopto.net/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>After study a few of the blog posts on your website now, and I truly like your way of blogging. I bookmarked it to my bookmark website list and will be checking back soon. Pls check out my web site as well and let me know what you think.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="46895b0c-61ec-44eb-9171-c826fb7c87c7" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-04-11 14:30:35</date>
      <author>internet directory</author>
      <email>Moro@bbc.co.uk</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>5.157.49.222</ip>
      <website>http://www.shorte.net/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>Aw, this was a really nice post. In idea I would like to put in writing like this additionally – taking time and actual effort to make a very good article… but what can I say… I procrastinate alot and by no means seem to get something done.</content>
    </comment>
    <comment id="a5e81229-2704-4e8a-b567-f164e637f208" parentid="00000000-0000-0000-0000-000000000000" approved="False" spam="True" deleted="False">
      <date>2015-05-06 23:06:47</date>
      <author>seo directory</author>
      <email>Mcmorran@manchester.ac.uk</email>
      <country>us</country>
      <ip>213.184.125.83</ip>
      <website>http://www.urldirecting.com/</website>
      <moderatedby>App_Code.Extensions.StopForumSpam</moderatedby>
      <avatar />
      <content>This really answered my problem, thank you!</content>
    </comment>
  </comments>
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>