<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<post>
  <author>MilesGuru</author>
  <title>7 Habits of Obsessive Airline Mile Collectors</title>
  <description />
  <content>&lt;p&gt;There are travelers and then there are Travelers. There are those who spend a great portion of their time planning each upcoming trip to the last detail, hunting down the best hotels, resorts and airline deals, and making great sport of accumulating large quantities of airline miles. For these travelers, there are few greater pleasures in life than getting a round-trip ticket to a choice destination free of charge. They consistently book flights with airline miles, and rarely pay for tickets.&amp;nbsp;If this sounds appealing, but far-fetched--it really isn't. These people have simply made a serious past time out of collecting airline miles. For people who are seriously wanting to book flights with airline miles,&amp;nbsp;these are the 7 habits that can help make it happen:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are basically two ways to earn airline miles: &amp;nbsp;1. Book flights 2. Spend money&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is an oversimplification, however. There are plenty of folks who book flights with&amp;nbsp;airline miles without flying. Here's how they do it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Credit cards.&lt;/b&gt; Signing up for a credit card is one of the easiest ways to accumulate points. Most mileage credit cards also have a deal that offers "bonus" miles just for signing up. These bonuses can be up to 35,000 miles or more.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dining out.&lt;/b&gt; Many airlines offer dining programs that give you points for every dollar you spend at a participating restaurant.&amp;nbsp;Simply register for the program and link up a&amp;nbsp;credit card (the one that earns&amp;nbsp;miles!)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Shopping.&lt;/b&gt; Most airline programs offer shopping "portals" to many&amp;nbsp;popular&amp;nbsp;retailers. Just&amp;nbsp;log in through a&amp;nbsp;frequent flyer miles account, and shop online.&amp;nbsp;This does not cost&amp;nbsp;anything extra, and it's possible to earn&amp;nbsp;anywhere from 1 to 5 or more miles for every dollar&amp;nbsp;spent. Many people are able to book flights with airline miles by purchasing everyday items through these programs.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Promotions&lt;/b&gt;. It can take some digging around, but there are plenty of companies that offer promotions to sign up or try products and services that will reward people with airline miles.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hotels&lt;/b&gt;. Similar to the dining programs, many hotels partner with airlines and offer up miles for money spent staying at their hotels. Again, check the airlines to find out what hotels qualify for this, there are a wide variety to choose, from economy inns to luxury resorts.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;When people do book flights with airline miles, they often look for special promotions and offers given by airlines that can result in more miles. Reading the fine print is mandatory here, but there are great deals to be had.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Financial institutions &lt;/b&gt;often offer up bonus miles for signing up for an account or a service. This can be a bit labor-intensive, but many find it's worth it when they are able to book flights with airline miles.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To book flights with airline miles it simply takes finding the best returns for dollars spent, whether it is with dining, car rentals or credit card fees. The fastest route is usually credit card sign-ups, then using the cards to make purchases that earn miles. There are plenty of people who book flights with airline miles and don't ever pay for their flights.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
  <ispublished>True</ispublished>
  <isdeleted>True</isdeleted>
  <iscommentsenabled>True</iscommentsenabled>
  <pubDate>2014-03-25 11:03:00</pubDate>
  <lastModified>2014-03-25 08:40:57</lastModified>
  <raters>0</raters>
  <rating>0</rating>
  <slug>7-habits-of-obsessive-airline-mile-collectors</slug>
  <tags />
  <comments />
  <categories />
  <notifications />
</post>